{
    "id": "525f232594e24d7f8a7f569bd6504485",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I think ................................... time to call it quits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it's",
                "its"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9742e6231c7b44cf9cae1099483ecf66"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ............................... do you speak English?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6000332c0b004d1a8dbc1335431ff2c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like that teacher. She is ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21266dc80803480d98329dacd8f38a97"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks ..................................... French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eeb2107b87a740aeb401aa6e91402992"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got longer hair ................................ I have.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d7683cbc62d4c0b914629f944a853f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He attributed the failure of the project to .................................... lack of appeal to the masses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it's",
                "its"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da396a188312436b8fc613a38e8608b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. is a bridge across the river.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Their",
                "There"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d9a8c0a973e43e0bbc9d17757436443"
        },
        {
            "question": "They sent more food .................................. I had ordered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab1ef6c56d614404b4bb4210a4348702"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know anybody ................................... going to London in the next few weeks?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcb3ee18458c4ae38af8a5c6c156ca79"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... coat is this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whose",
                "Who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5ff3d5eedf140ddac13fb24b31ae8e3"
        }
    ]
}